I don't want you to go anywhere.
You're so unfair.
I was actually to let you go.
Why are you looking at me?
Because you're cute.
Woof-woof.
Book.
Are you starting to like me yet?
I'll give in to you just for today.
I'm exhausted.
Me too.
But I think it's great.
Really great.
Hey.
Can I sleep over at your house?
Sleep over?
You should go back and sleep at your house.
It's my house.
I've already slept there.
But at your house--
You already slept at my house before.
You should go back.
Can I sleep over at your place?
Can I?
What are you doing?
Hello, Jie Fing.
It's late now.
Can I sleep over at your place?
Um.
Of course.
Come on in.
Hey, Jie.
Thank you.
Um.
(Ma) You can't do it like that.
(Pa) Why does it always go too far?
Are you gonna say that's beacuse you're too good?
Yeah, absolutely.
Why do you trim the head off?
Pa, Ma, I'm back.
You're back.
Hello.
I really miss you.
Tee, you can join us.
Okay.
Alright, we're complete.
You take advantage of the situation.
I miss you, honey.
How was your day? Is it tired?
Whoa, you see right through me.
Does anyone want to give me a hand
with these bean sprouts?
Nah.
Does no one want to help me?
It's all yours.
I'll help you.
Help me?
Yes, help you with these bean sprouts.
Hmm?
May I help you?
Wow.
He can really do it.
He even does it smoothly.
Pa, look.
(Ma) So, you like eating bean sprouts.
(Pa) I'd better do something else.
Oh.
Where are you going?
Wow, you're leaving.
I'm leaving.
Tee, do you like bean sprouts?
I like them.
I'd better fix a floor lamp. It keeps flickering.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I'll help you.
Huh?
Can you fix it?
I can.
So talented.
You can do anything from trimming
bean sprouts to fixing the lamp.
Thanks, thanks.
Um.
Let me help you.
Thank you, Tee.
You're the best.
Tee, you're so nice.
Thanks for saying that.
Unlike a kid around here.
Huh?
Huh? Look, he's helping us.
Well, would you consider me your son?
Why not?
I want to have a good-looking son
like you for a long time.
I'm good-looking too, right?
Yeah, you're good-looking.
My lil monkey.
But Tee is more good-looking.
But I think... Papa is the most good-looking.
Aww.
Now you're talking.
You can stay with me as long as you want.
Can he be your son?
Hold on.
Take him to the kitchen. I want to see
whether he can prep ingredients or not.
If he can, I'll accept him as my son.
Really?
Yeah.
Let's head over.
Go, go.
Come over here.
Will you accept him as our son?
Well, let's see.
Let's go.
Fuse.
I'd better go see Tee.
Tee~
Tee!
You're being extra.
Wow. You look good from every angle,
like me in my old days.
Do you think he's as handsome as you?
Um.
Like you in your old days?
Yeah, like looking in the mirror.
I can't remember that.
Eh?
Hmph.
You...
You used to compliment me.
Now, you're getting old and...
starting to lose your memories.
Hey, come on.
How could you forget how handsome I am?
It's like looking in the mirror.
Okay, go back to your seat.
Hmm?
What do you mean I'm losing my memories?
Fuse, go back to your seat.
Back to your seat.
Come over here.
By the way...
You're really handsome, Tee.
With a face like that,
girls must be all over you, right?
Tee.
Are you dating anyone?
Ma.
Gen Z doesn't just become
a couple easily these days.
They have to pass a
talking stage before becoming a couple.
They're a couple, but they define
themselves as being in the talking stage?
Not a couple, they just seeing each other.
Wait, in that case...
that's called leading someone on.
Yeah.
If they refuse to use the word "couple"...
and play the field,
that means they keep their
options open to see what works.
Is that right, Tee?
Hmm?
I feel like...
If I like someone,
I only have eyes for them.
There you go.
Ma, you see?
Besides being handsome,
he's as faithful and loyal as I am.
Um.
That's so sweet.
Look at your dad.
He suddenly turned
the conversation back to himself.
Ma, fight back. Don't let him win.
Nah.
Tee.
Yes?
I'll tell you what.
If our family goes on a trip,
you must come with us. Okay?
Sure.
Let's eat.
Here are the bean sprouts that Tee had trimmed.
Alright.
It's time to eat.
Tee.
What is that on your shirt?
Well, I went to help Pa carry a flower pot.
I see.
You're serving my dad too much.
Your dad can't carry it by himself.
That's true.
The bathroom is free. Go take a shower before Jie.
Or you'll have to wait for a long time.
Take it.
(Jeen) Are you home now?
(Jeen) I'm still at Siam.
You've been there so long.
Who are you with?
I... I'm with my friend.
Well, did you and Tee
go seperate ways heading home?
Why?
Well...
Just in case we hang out with him again.
I think...
I might invite my friend next time.
So it'll be a double date.
My friend is cute, and she has a lot of followers.
I think Tee will like her.
This is mine.
And yours is...
This one.
Which one is better?
The red one.
Look.
Jeen.
I need to talk to you.
I have to go now. I'll let you know
when I'm at home. Bye.
Hey.
I only like you.
But I understand that…
it's impossible for us.
Can you dry my hair?
Who are you asking me to do that?
I'll be anything...
you want me to be.
Fine.
Turn around.
Ouch, that's too hard.
Oh, sorry.
You're just messing with me.
Tee.
Why do you have such broad shoulders?
Do you like them?
Nah, I didn't say that.
So you don't like them?
You don't have to answer. I'm just joking around.
Oh, he posted the pictures.
Wait, let me see.
Whoa, he also posted my pic.
Hey.
Why don't you keep your pics?
I don't want to keep mine.
I want to keep ours.
Stop it.
Did she just call?
Do you mean Jeen?
Um.
She wants to invite you to go out.
So she could introduce her friend to you.
Her friend is cute, though.
She has a lot of followers, just in case you like it.
I only like you.
But I understand that...
it's impossible for us.
I feel uncomfortable.
I'm uncomfortable that...
I don't know what should I do.
What do you want to do the most, then?
I want to be with you.
Right here.
Why not?
I'm here.
[What are you guys doing tonight?]
[That's cute.]
[Whose fortune is this?]
[Answer my DM, please.]
[Won't your partner be jealous of posting this pic?]
[Aren't you cold? I can give you a hug.]
[Delete it.]
[Stop it, or I'll block you.]
[Loudly crying face emojis]
[Others can only look, but you already touched it.
Isn't that enough?]
[Skull emojis]
Hurry up, everybody.
Hurry up.
Alright.
Did I leave my bag?
Where are you going?
What?
I already told you guys yesterday.
You talked about a lot of things yesterday.
Hmm?
I mean about our trip.
Tee already agreed to go on a trip together.
Hmm?
If our family goes on a trip,
you must come with us. Okay?
Sure.
Today?
Yeah, today.
I'll call Tee's family and let them know.
Thank you.
And let Yaimai's family know as well.
So, where are we going?
Khao Yai!
What?
Let's go, I really want to go.
Fine, let's go.
Yay!
That's more like it!
The weather is also perfect.
Go change quickly.
Let's go.
Go, go.
So cute.
I really like it.
Do you like rabbits?
I like you.
Fuse! What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
You got a problem with that?
What are you gonna do about it?
Take it.
Are you teasing me?
What are you guys doing?
-Nothing.
-Nothing
Don't let me find out you're teasing each other.
(Jeen) Fuse, where are you? I miss you so much.
I'm...
Right, have you seen
the perfume-making workshop that I shared?
Shall we go there?
I'd like you to help me with it
so I can make the scent that you like.
Well...
I'll head out after my shower.
I'll be there in less than an hour.
I'm afraid we can't go today.
I'm at Khao Yai with my family.
Oh, really?
I'm sorry.
Um.
It's fine.
Let's do it another time.
Okay.
Oh.
What's up?
I'm just checking on you.
But I think I'd better go.
Tee.
We should get back. Pa and Ma are waiting.
I just want to be with you.
Even though tomorrow…
you'll get back with Jeen,
I'll still be happy today anyway.
-Pa.
-Hmm?
Are we being scammed?
I doubt it.
The tense vibe in here,
I like it.
But I think...
it's changed quite a lot.
There have been some
renovations and changes outside.
But the mood in the room...
I know you still remember...
every single corner of it.
Don't pretend you don't know that.
Pa.
I should hurry up and grab our room key.
I really want to get inside the room.
Ma.
This place is so beautiful.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Shall we go take some pictures?
Great.
Let's go over there.
The pics will be stunning if taken with a flashlight.
Okay.
I'll take a picture of you.
Let's go.
Where are we going again?
It looks beautiful over there.
Ma, stand and pose right there.
Fuse.
Hmm?
Do you think we will share a room?
Why?
I want to share a room with you.
Hey.
So I can do things more easily.
Tee.
I mean using a restroom.
Your house is full of women.
I don't want to intrude.
I think my dad reserved a few rooms.
That's great.
In case I hug you in my sleep,
so your family won't be shocked at it.
Tee.
Ouch.
Then I'll share a room with my sis.
And you'll share a room with my dad.
Hey, don't do that.
Ma, please check the pictures.
Are they good?
That's great.
How to say it again? Serving?
Serving looks.
So Gen Z.
Whoa.
Alright, here you go.
Here.
Thank you.
And this is...
our room.
Fing, can I take a shower first today?
I also want to take a shower first.
Whoever arrives first gets to shower first.
Fing, hurry up.
Fuse, Tee, go to your room and get some rest.
See you later.
Okay.
Let's head over.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Let's check...
whether the room is still the same.
I'm leaving.
It's time to reminisce.
Don't be scared.
I won't do anything to you tonight,
if you don't consent.
Tee.
Take the stuff. I'm off.
Fuse, wait for me.
Ugh.
My whole body is sore.
I guess it's because I carry too much handsomeness.
Don't you think?
I'm happy.
You're happy?
For carrying the whole stuff?
I like being with you.
Are you really happy?
Yeah.
Liar.
If you're not okay,
you don't have to pretend to be okay.
I'm really okay with this.
I expect nothing.
I just want to be with you.
Even though tomorrow...
you'll get back with Jeen,
I'll still be happy today anyway.
Take it easy.
How much you give me, that's all I'll accept.
These two days are all mine.
Fine.
Then, how about your day?
Maybe like this.
Tee.
Um.
If you want to be with me,
take me to get something to eat.
I'm hungry.
Eat me.
I'm yummy.
You can try.
Okay.
Yummy, huh?
Come on, Tee.
Let's grab something to eat.
Let's go.
Come on, hurry up.
Come on.
Ma, Pa.
Can we join you guys?
Of course.
Do you like the room?
Um.
Is it good?
The room is still beautiful as before.
Like I told you.
Have you been here before?
Look.
I'll tell you what.
After we had married,...
I brought your mom here...
for our honeymoon.
We were staying in your room.
Right,...
you...
almost got a sister named after Khao Yai.
Pa.
Don't tell them.
I've already planned it.
If you are married,
I'll reserve a room at this place.
As your wedding gift and your honeymoon.
So your love will last long, like Pa and Ma's love.
You went too far. He's just in 11th grade.
And he's not dating anyone, right?
Yes.
See?
It's okay.
Let's take this as a practice honeymoon with Tee.
Hey, I'm joking.
Um.
Well,...
I won't bother you guys anymore.
Get some rest and relax.
Because...
I'll take her to...
get some rest as well.
Reminiscing, reminiscing.
I can't with him.
Well, if you guys have se...
Oh.
If you guys need anything,
let me know.
I'll take care of you.
Let's go.
Let's head over to our room.
Hurry up. Leave the kids alone.
Let's go.
See you later.
Thank you.
Feel free to knock on my door anytime.
I'll take care of you.
Don't knock it too loud.
Let's practice a honeymoon.
Hurry up.
Come on, let's practice.
We should practice a honeymoon.
What's wrong?
Are you sulking because I don't take a shower with you?
No.
The bathroom is too small.
Hmm, Tee.
No.
Fine.
I'll make it up to you.
Come over here.
Let's play a game.
Come on.
No.
Fine.
I'll give you a massage.
Aren't you tired after sitting in a car for too long?
Hmm?
No.
Whoa.
You're so sulky.
I say nothing.
I give a great massage, Mr. Tee.
Sorry, sir.
My mom sent me a message.
What did she say?
[Time for bed, kids. Stop playing around.]
(Ma) Time for bed, kids. Stop playing around.
Your family is so lovely.
Your parents are really kind.
Jie Fing is also funny.
It's more like a chaotic family.
What about your family?
I've only ever met Tim.
Do you mean my parents?
Um.
Not only have you never met them,
but I have rarely met them either.
My parents are busy.
So I often stay with Tim.
Are you lonely?
I used to think that I'm not lonely.
After meeting your family,...
I realize mine is lonely.
Hey, every home has its own vibe.
Don't compare.
Sometimes...
I just want some quiet time like you.
It's so peaceful.
So,...
Whenever you want a quiet time,
you can come to my house.
Um.
And whenever I want to be surrounded by people,
I'll go to your house. Is that a deal?
Good idea.
Deal.
I couldn't be happier.
I could die right now.
Hey.
You couldn't.
My mom tells me that
saying good words brings good things.
Got it?
Fuse.
What?
I'm saying good words.
I'm not a good thing.
I'm just good-looking.
I'm gonna sleep.
Tee, am I not good-looking?
Tee.
Why am I not handsome?
What makes you think like that?
Hey, don't fall asleep yet.
Get up and explain.
Hmm?
Hey, Tee.
So you posted those pics…
just to get people to like you?
If that's all you want,
you can deactivate your account.
I can do it for you.
Hello, baby.
I'm waiting to buy grilled pork skewers.
I know you like it, baby.
If I buy you ten grilled pork skewers,
can I kiss you on the cheek ten times?
I have to go, baby.
Can I have ten grilled pork skewers, please?
Ten?
Kissing on the cheek ten times?
Can I have ten grilled pork skewers, please?
Ten grilled pork skewers?
Yes.
Okay.
Wait, can I have fifty grilled pork skewers, please?
Fifty?
Yes, please.
Okay.
Do you buy them for your partner?
Yes.
I'm asking who you keep transferring money to?
Mind your own business and go raise your child.
He's going to take the admission tests next year.
Have you ever taken care of him?
You do still remember that...
our son will take the exam next year.
Then why did you have an affair with a university girl?
How disgusting!
She is about our son's age.
Just keep your nose out of it.
Give me your phone.
Who did you send the money to?
Leave me alone.
It's that girl, right?
It's my phone.
Give it to me now.
Who is she?
Stay out of this.
Hey.
You're being too loud.
Excuse me.
Yes?
I saw Aedes mosquitoes.
They are over there.
They're this huge.
-That huge?
-Yes.
Over there?
Yes.
Okay, I got it.
You have to kill them right now.
Okay.
Where I go is none of your business.
It has nothing to do with you.
I told you to send money to our son.
Just one call from her and you send her money?
Give it to me. Ugh!
Let's talk about it later.
No more next time, come here.
Give me your phone.
Are you going to see her again? Come here!
Book.
Don't pout.
It's not cute.
Let's get inside.
Book, did you delete the photo last night?
I deleted it.
Huh?
For real?
Gosh.
You really deleted it.
Because of me?
Actually,...
you don't have to post pics like that.
Look.
You can post a pic of yourself
eating grilled pork skewers.
Will people like it?
What do you care?
Whatever you post..
or complain about...
is your business.
Screw everyone else.
If you post those pics...
because you want to,
I'm okay with it.
But if you're posting them because people like them,
I think it doesn't work.
You don't understand.
How could I understand...
if you don't tell me?
(Book's mom) Book.
(Book's mom) Haven't you finished it yet?
How could you go to
a competition with this writing speed?
(Book's dad) Why can't you pass
the school entrance exam?
Lots of people pass it.
Did you really put effort into it?
Ugh.
You're no good.
Because I'm never good enough for anyone.
But in that world,...
people like me.
At least,
[Cute.] [So good.]
those pics make some people like me.
[Three hundred baht if taking it lower.]
Otherwise, I would...
So, you posted those pics...
just to get people to like you?
If that's all you want,
you can deactivate your account.
I can do it for you.
I like you not because of those pics.
I like you...
beacuse of here.
I like you for who you are.
For being a class rep.
You know what,...
every time you write down my name,...
I feel so happy.
Because I want my name...
in your book.
You're so flirty.
I might be a flirt,
but I only flirt with you.
Come over here.
You can let your guard down...
when you're with me.
[singing "HIT ME UP" by TIMETHAI.]
Hey, when did you get here?
What's got into you?
Are you wearing that to go home?
Nah, this is for playing in the water.
Playing in the water?
Can I join ?
Where are your clothes for playing in the water?
I didn't bring them.
But I can take this off now.
Hold on, wait.
Tee.
You don't have to.
You can borrow mine.
I can take this off.
No, no.
Stop it.
Ugh, Tee!
Is the water cold?
Yeah, I want to play it now.
Then jump in.
Hey, I can't.
Do you see a bird?
I don't.
You're trying so hard to act cool.
Whose man is this?
I didn't try.
But I...
just born to be like this.
Tee, won't you play in the water?
Whoa.
Are they Fuse's shorts?
You look so handsome in those.
Thank you.
You agree?
Totally.
When you're handsome, you can wear anything.
For who is not handsome,
even though wearing sunglasses,
wearing shirt,
wearing shorts,
that person still...
Still what?
Say it if you dare.
Still not handsome!
Hey.
Chill out.
Relax, Fuse.
You mad?
Whoa!
Fuse!
We're all wet!
Take it.
It splashed to me earlier.
All over your body?
Yeah.
It won't be fun if we don't get wet.
I'm all wet.
That's still not enough.
Jie.
Huh?
Where is Tee?
Tee?
He's over that duck pool float.
Oh.
Where is he now?
Tee...
Hey, is he over there?
Oh!
Tee!
Hey.
Hey, wait.
Yes?
You have a practice today, right?
Fuse is really good.
He can do everything I taught him.
Fuse, who is she?
Is she Tee's girlfriend?
She's my girlfriend.
I have seen your happiness for the first time.
She's so cute.
What if she isn't my happiness?
I do understand that
she's done something unfair to you first.
But you shouldn't have done that to her.
I think...
I will ask her to break up.